

01753-142981

afsana1996sultana@gmail.com 🔀

Ka-55 Shajadpur, Gulshan, Dhaka 🥊

https://github.com/afsana1996sultana 🔛

https://www.linkedin.com/in/afsana-sultana-0a399915b in

## **About Me**

I aim to attain an engaging as a software Engineer position in the software development. The effective utilize of knowledge, skills and experience for the organization development as well as for social well being. Honest and determined to engage and completion of a project. Keeping updated with the latest technology. Believe in active learning. And build up my career as a software engineer.

## **Skills**

- Project Management
- Problem Solving
- Creativity
- Leadership
- Communication Skills

# **Expertise**

- UI/UX
- Web Design
- Laravel (MVC)
- Javascript

# **Work Experience**

### 2021 -2022 Jr.Software Engineer | Syscon Solution LTD

Multi Vendor E-Commerce Website (SYSCON): A website with multiple users, admins, customers & vendors can access by their role Id. All kinds of products are shown in the website by their category, sub-category, child-category and their brand.

Wishlist, Add-to-cart, Quick-view, Process-to-checkout, Coupon code, Campaign, Advertisement, Order, Payment-method, Shipping etc all kinds of features like other e-commerce websites have are available in this multi vendor e-commerce website.

Technology: Laravel, JS (Jauery, Ajax), PHP, MySal.

#### Jr.Software Engineer | Syscon Solution LTD 2021 -2022

A company website of Syscon Engineering LTD.

(https://www.sysconbd.com). This website contains various information of Syscon Engineering Ltd, their business units and their business policy. And all features are loaded dynamically in the site.

Technology: Laravel, JS (Jauery, Ajax), PHP, MySal.

#### 2021 - 2022 Jr.Software Engineer | Syscon Solution LTD

A Web Application (Dhaka Wasa):

A web application made by .Net in visual studio. This application can read write the data from the machine and calculate the average value in a particular time.

Technology: C#, ASP.Net, MVC, SQLServer.

# Special Qualification/Training

Skill Development for Mobile Game & Application Project.

Topic: App design, development, database, sign Apk, add google map.

Institute: Sheikh Kamal IT Training & Incubation Center Natore.

Duration: 200 hours.

### Web Design & Development.

Topic: Html, CSS, JS, PHP, Bootstrap (basic). Institute: IT Next Home Training Institute Natore.

Duration: 200 hours.

#### Graphics Design.

Topic: Background change, photo edit, banner design, logo & business card

Institute: Sheikh Kamal IT Training & Incubation Center Natore.

Duration: 200 hours.

# **Education**

2016-2020 BSC in CSE (Computer Science & Engineering)

4 years Rajshahi Science & Technology University (RSTU) Natore

Bachelor Of Science

Computer Science & Engineering

CGPA: 3.86 (Out of 4.00)

2012-2014 Higher Secondary Certificate (H. S. C)

2 years Govt. Women's College Pabna

Science

GPA: 3.63 (Scale of 5.00)

2011-2012 Secondary School Certificate (S. S. C)

2 years Shahid M. Monsur Ali High School Pabna

Science

GPA: 4.44 (Scale of 5.00)

## Reference

### **Dewan Juel Rahman**

Assistant Professor & Chairman

Dept. of CSE (Computer Science & Engineering)

Rajshahi Science & Technology University (RSTU) Natore.

Phone: +8801815469046

Email: juelrstu@gmail.com